A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, New York Office, Series 22 FA365
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appointments Office, 1959-1965; 1; 9 Cubic Feet
  - Buffalo, New York; Jamestown, New York, January 14, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 603)
    Buffalo 1. Industrial labor Relations Meeting 2. Regional Development of Erie, Niagara, and Wyoming Counties Jamestown 1. Regional Development of Cattaraugus and Chautauqua Counties
  - New York, New York, January 15, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 604)
    1. New York State Science and Technology Foundation
  - Albany, New York, January 17, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 605)
    1. New York State Association for Mental Health
  - Washington, DC, January 20, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 606)
    Inauguration of President Lyndon Johnson
  - New York, New York, January 21, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 607)
    1. Westchester Republican County Committee
  - New York, New York; Washington, DC, January 23, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 608)
    New York City 1. Foundation for Research of the New York Academy - Medallion of Honor Washington, D.C. 1. Alfalfa Club Dinner
  - New York, New York, January 27, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 609)
    1. Memorial Dinner for Jawaharlal Nehru
  - Princeton, New Jersey, January 28, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 610)
    1. Private dinner
  - New York, New York, January 29, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 611)
    1. Adolfe Berle 70th Birthday luncheon
  - New York, New York, January 30, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 612)
  - New York, New York, January 31, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 613)
    1. Memorial Service for Winston Churchill
  - Regrets, January 1965 (Box 19, Folder 614)
    1. New York State Chamber of Commerce Executives 2. Dedication of Warren Weaver Hall, New York City 3. Franciscan Brothers Guild of Brooklyn
  - Albany, New York, February 2, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 615)
    1. Department of Public Works Luncheon 2. New York State Republican Committee Executive Committee 3. Empire State Chamber of Commerce
  - Rochester, New York, February 4, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 616)
    1. Regional Development Luncheon 2. Nuclear Structures Laboratory
  - Albany, New York, February 7, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 617)
  - New York, New York, February 9, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 618)
    1. Association of Towns of the State of New York 2. Association of Fire Districts
  - Hornell, New York, February 11, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 619)
    1. Bath - Veterans Administration Hospital 2. Department of Public Works Headquarters 3. New York Agricultural and Technical College 4. Hornell Chamber of Commerce Dinner
  - Albany, New York, February 16, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 620)
    1. American Jewish Congress 2. American Legion Legislative Dinner
  - Washington, DC, February 23, 1965; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, February 24, 1965; Washington, DC, February 24, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 621)
    February 23 - Washington, D.C. 1. Congressional Committee Hearing February 24 - Philadelphia 1. Delaware River Basin Commission February 24 - Washington, D.C. 1. Congressional Delegation Dinner
  - Regrets, February 1965 (Box 20, Folder 622)
    1. 300th Anniversary of Duke's Law Convention 2. Queens County American Legion 3. Columbia County Young Republican Club 4. New York City Elementary School Principals
  - Albany, New York, March 1, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 623)
    1. League of Women Voters of New York State 2. New York State Council of Churches
  - Albany, New York, March 2, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 624)
  - Albany, New York, March 3, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 625)
    1. Associated Industries of New York State
  - Binghamton, New York, March 4, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 626)
    1. Binghamton State Hospital 2. Kirkwood Industrial Park 3. Press conference 4. Chamber of Commerce Luncheon 5. Meeting with representatives of WBJA-TV 6. Meeting with local Republican leaders 7. WBNF-TV panel show 8. Meeting with "Binghamton Press" editorial board 9. Meeting with "Binghamton Sun" editorial board
  - Washington, DC; New York, New York, March 5, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 627)
    Washington 1. National Wildlife Federation New York City 1. New York Young Republican Club
  - New York, New York, March 6, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 628)
  - Trenton, New Jersey, March 9, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 629)
    1. Meeting with Governor Hughes
  - Washington, DC, March 10, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 630)
    1. Breakfast with Governor Smylie 2. Republican Coordinating Committee 3. American Institute for Free Labor Development 4. Senate Committee Testimony
  - Albany, New York, March 11, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 631)
  - Albany, New York, March 15, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 632)
  - New York, New York, March 17, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 633)
    1. St. Patrick's Day Parade (reviewing stand) 2. Friendly Sons of St. Patrick Dinner
  - New York, New York, March 18, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 634)
    1. United Jewish Appeal Dinner
  - Albany, New York, March 20, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 635)
  - New York, New York, March 26, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 636)
    1. Luncheon with Governors John H. Chaffee of Rhode Island, John A. Volpe of Massachusetts, John H. Dempsey of Connecticut to discuss New Haven Railroad
  - Grossinger's, New York, March 30, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 637)
    1. County Officers Association (canceled)
  - Pending, March 1965 (Box 20, Folder 638)
    1. New York Young Republican Club 2. New York State Broadcasters Club 3. National Council of Christians and Jews
  - Regrets, March 1965 (Box 20, Folder 639)
    1. Connecticut Intercollegiate Student Legislature 2. Veterans of Foreign Wars, Annual Gold Chevron Ball 3. National Council of Jewish Women
  - Watertown, New York; Massena, New York, April 1, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 640)
    Watertown 1. Fisher Gauge Co. Plant 2. News conference 3. Chamber of Commerce Luncheon 4. "Watertown Times" 5. WCNY-TV panel taping Massena 1. Chamber of Commerce Dinner and Reception
  - Albany, New York, April 7, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 641)
    1. Administrative Council of Department of Labor
  - New York, New York, April 8, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 642)
    1. Dedication of Path Service, Journal Square
  - Albany, New York, April 12, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 643)
    1. "Executive Chamber" Dinner
  - New York, New York, April 19, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 644)
    1. Reception with the Editors of "Newsweek"
  - New York, New York, April 21, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 645)
    1. Reopening of New York Worlds Fair
  - New York, New York, April 22, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 646)
    1. New York State Day at the Worlds Fair 2. Dinner for Aldo Moro (NAR sent remarks)
  - New York, New York, April 26, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 647)
    1. American National Theatre and Academy
  - Ithaca, New York; Kingston, New York, April 27, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 648)
    Ithaca 1. Cornell University Charter Day Kingston 1. Lions Club Annual Exposition and Home Show
  - New York, New York, April 28, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 649)
    1. Mount Sinai School of Medicine
  - New York, New York, April 29, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 650)
    1. Association of radio-Television News Analysts
  - Pending, April 1965 (Box 20, Folder 651)
    1. National Conference of Christians and Jews
  - Regrets, April 1965 (Box 20, Folder 652)
  - Delhi, New York, May 1, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 653)
    1. Dedication of State University College at Delhi
  - New York, New York, May 6, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 654)
    1. American Women in Radio and Television
  - New York, New York, May 7, 1965; Watkins Glen, New York, May 7-8, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 655)
    New York City 1. Governor's Conference on the Aging Watkins Glen - May 7 1. Filming of the Governor Watkins Glen - May 8 1. Filming of the Governor
  - Cleveland, Ohio, May 10, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 656)
    1. Great Lakes Basin Pollution Conference
  - Albany, New York, May 11, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 657)
    1. American Society for Public Administration
  - New York, New York, May 13, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 658)
    1. Inauguration of Samuel Brookner Gould as President of the State University of New York
  - Livingston Manor, New York, May 15, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 659)
  - Albany, New York, May 18, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 660)
    1. New York State Women's Civil Defense Council
  - NOT USED (Box 21, Folder 661)
  - New York, New York; Garden City, New York, May 20, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 662)
    New York City 1. New York State Council on the Arts at the World's Fair 2. Society of Foreign Consuls in New York 3. Press Photographers Association of New York Garden City 1. Nassau County Republican Dinner
  - New York, New York, May 23, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 663)
    1. Fashion Institute of Technology Dinner
  - Newburgh, New York; Huntingdon, New York, May 27, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 664)
    Newburgh 1. Mount St. Mary College a. Press conference b. Luncheon, Chamber of Commerce Huntingdon 1. Oyster Bay - cocktails with John H. G. Pell 2. Long Island Festival Dinner of the Long Island Arts Center
  - Pending, May 1965 (Box 21, Folder 665)
    1. Delaware County Republican Committee
  - Washington, DC, June 1, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 666)
    1. Republican Coordinating Committee
  - New York, New York, June 3, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 667)
    1. Inter-American Association for Democracy and Freedom
  - New York, New York, June 6, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 668)
    1. Puerto Rican Day Parade
  - New York, New York, June 7, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 669)
    1. National Association of Tax Administrators (canceled)
  - New York, New York, June 8, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 670)
    1. National Association of Insurance Commissioners
  - New York, New York, June 10, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 671)
  - New York, New York, June 11, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 672)
    1. National Federation of Republican Women 2. Governor's Committee on "Employ the Handicapped"
  - Rockland County, New York, June 15, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 673)
    1. Pearl River - Lederle Laboratories Ceremonies 2. Rockland Lake North Park Ceremonies 3. Orangeburg - Tappan Zee Historical Society 4. Suffern - Geigy Chemical Corporation
  - Rochester, New York, June 16, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 674)
    1. New York State Conference of Mayors and other Municipal Officials
  - Chemung County, New York; New York, New York, June 17, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 675)
    Chemung County 1. Chamber of Commerce Luncheon New York City 1. 75th Birthday party for Jane Todd
  - Washington, DC, June 18, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 676)
    1. Arts Councils of America, Inc.
  - Albany, New York, June 21, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 677)
    1. Cornerstone Laying, South Mall
  - New York, New York, June 22, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 678)
    1. United Jewish Appeal Headquarters
  - Albany, New York, June 24, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 679)
    1. Governor's Library Conference
  - Pending, June 1965 (Box 21, Folder 680)
    1. Republican Coordinating Committee 2. Annual Dinner of the City of Hope 3. National Association of Insurance Commissioners
  - Regrets, June 1965 (Box 21, Folder 681)
    1. American Association of Law Libraries
  - Niagara Falls, New York, July 16, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 682)
    1. Maid of the Mist Annual Ball
  - Minneapolis, Minnesota, July 25-26, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 683)
    July 25 1. WCCO-TV, "Face the Nation" appearance 2. Luncheon with vice President and Mrs. Hubert Humphrey 3. Republican Party of Minnesota 4. Geneva Association Reception and Dinner July 26 1. Republican Governor's Association Breakfast 2. Press conference 3. State luncheon 4. Conference sessions 5. Reception and dinner
  - Pending, July 1965 (Box 21, Folder 684)
    1. State Commission for Human Rights
  - Smithtown, New York, August 8, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 685)
    1. News conference, luncheon 2. Smithtown Tri-Centennial Parade
  - Buffalo, New York, August 10, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 686)
    1. Federal Water Pollution Conference
  - Orange County, New York; Chenango County, New York; St. Lawrence County, New York, August 14, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 687)
    Orange County 1. Orange County Fair Chenango County 1. Chenango County Fair St. Lawrence County 1. St. Lawrence County Fair
  - New York, New York, August 14, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 688)
    1. Annual Convention of the Hadassah
  - Camp Drum, New York; Monroe County, New York; Steuben County, New York, August 14, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 689)
    Camp Drum 1. Review of 27th Armored Division Monroe County 1. Monroe County Fair Steuben County 1. Route 17, Southern Tier Expressway Project 2. Steuben County Republican Picnic
  - Fort Schuyler, The Bronx, New York, August 24, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 690)
    1. State University of New York at Fort Schuyler a. Inspection, Training Ship "Empire State IV" b. Words of Welcome
  - Dutchess County, New York; New York, New York, August 25, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 691)
    Dutchess County 1. Dutchess County Fair New York City 1. WCBS-TV Water Program Documentary
  - Monroe and Onondaga Counties, New York, September 1-2, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 692)
    September 1 1. Rochester - St. John Fisher College Dedication 2. Syracuse - Annual State Farm Dinner September 2 1. Syracuse - Press conference 2. Syracuse - New York State Exposition
  - New York, New York, September 13, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 693)
    1. American Public Welfare Association
  - Westchester and Dutchess Counties, New York, September 16, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 694)
    1. Eastchester - Reception and luncheon, Yonkers Chamber of Commerce 2. Yonkers - New City Hall Building 3. Yonkers - Phillipse Towers Housing Project 4. Trevor Park - Proposed marina on the Hudson 5. Poughkeepsie-DeLaval Separator Plant
  - Albany, New York; New York, New York, September 17, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 695)
    Albany 1. Republican State Committee Luncheon 2. Greater Albany Chamber of Commerce New York City 1. Republican Women in Industry and Professions
  - New York, New York, September 19, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 696)
    1. Jewish Theological Seminary of America
  - Livingston County, New York, September 20, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 697)
    1. Livingston County Teachers Association 2. Sonyea-Craig Colony Hospital 3. State University College at Geneseo 4. News conference 5. Livingston County Republican Committee Dinner
  - New, New York; Seneca Falls, New York; Glens Falls, New York, September 21, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 698)
    New York City 1. County Officers Association of New York State 2. Saints and Sinners Luncheon Seneca Falls 1. Eisenhower College ground breaking, reception Glens Falls 1. New York State Association of Magistrates
  - Franklin County, New York, September 22, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 699)
    1. Sunmount - Sunmount Hospital 2. Tupper Lake - Women's Republican Club
  - New York, New York, September 23, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 700)
    1. WOR-TV taping, "Ladies of the Press"
  - New York, New York; Katonah, New York; Lake Placid, New York, September 24, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 701)
    New York City 1. Belgian Line Shipping Terminal dedication Katonah 1. John Jay Homestead Dedication Lake Placid 1. Associated Industries of New York State
  - New York, New York, September 25, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 702)
    1. Steuben Day Parade
  - Tarrytown, New York; New York, New York, September 27, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 703)
    Tarrytown 1. Interview with Walter Cronkite 2. Interview with reporters from WTEN-TV, Albany New York City 1. Old Metropolitan Opera House Opening
  - New York, New York, September 28, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 704)
    1. Federal Hudson River Pollution Enforcement 2. Sales Executives Club of New York
  - Erie and Jefferson Counties, New York; New York, New York, September 29, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 705)
    Erie and Jefferson Counties 1. Buffalo - Associated Press Managing Editors 2. Watertown - Interstate 81 dedication 3. Jefferson Community College dedication New York City 1. International Council of Museums 2. National Association of Retarded Children
  - Washington, DC, September 30, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 706)
    1. Reception and dinner at the residence of the Brazilian Ambassador to honor Mr. Richard Aldrich who was awarded the Order of the Southern Cross
  - New York, New York; Broome County, New York, October 1, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 707)
    New York City 1. All Column A Candidates (Republican Party) Broome County 1. Harpur College - Luncheon, press conference
  - New York, New York, October 3, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 708)
    1. Pulaski Day Parade (reviewing stand) 2. Reception by United States Ambassador to the United Nations Arthur Goldberg to honor President and Mrs. Lyndon Johnson
  - New York, New York, October 4, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 709)
    1. Papal Audience, St. Patrick's Cathedral 2. Mass for Peace, Yankee Stadium 3. American Association of Highway Officials 4. Reception for North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) Parliamentarians
  - New York, New York; Lake George, New York, October 5, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 710)
    New York City 1. Tour, Youth Opportunity Center Lake George 1. Adirondack Park Association
  - Niagara County, New York; Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada, October 6, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 711)
    Niagara County 1. Niagara Falls - Breakfast with Republicans 2. Lewiston - New section of Robert Moses Parkway Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada 1. Skylon Observatory Opening
  - Idaho, October 7-8, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 712)
    October 7 1. Boise - Press conference, airport 2. Boise - Governor's Mansion, reception 3. Caldwell - The College of Idaho, dinner, convocation, and reception October 8 1. Breakfast with President of College of Idaho 2. Student convocation at College of Idaho 3. Student coffee hour
  - New York, New York, October 11-12, 1965; Albany, New York, October 12, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 713)
    New York City - October 11 1. Annual Columbus Day Dinner New York City - October 12 1. Columbus Day Parade (reviewing stand) Albany, New York - October 12 1. Unveiling Bust of Christopher Columbus
  - New York, New York, October 13, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 714)
  - Madison, Wisconsin; Portland, Oregon, October 14, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 715)
    Madison, Wisconsin 1. Governor's Conference on Water Resources Management, meeting, luncheon Portland, Oregon 1. News conference 2. "Happy birthday, IKE" dinner
  - Atlanta, Georgia, October 17, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 716)
    1. Ebenezer Baptist Church, with Martin Luther King, Sr. and Jr. 2. Luncheon with the Dr. Martin Luther Kings (Sr. and Jr.)
  - New York, New York, October 18, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 717)
    1. Fordham University new school ground breaking 2. Luncheon with staff members of WCBS-TV
  - Binghamton, New York; Rochester, New York; Buffalo, New York, October 20, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 718)
    Binghamton 1. Susquehanna River Basin Study Committee Rochester 1. Inner Loop Highway Opening ceremonies Buffalo 1. Buffalo Academy of Medicine
  - Buffalo, New York; Albany, New York, October 21, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 719)
    Buffalo 1. Buffalo State Hospital new building 2. Roswell Park Memorial Institute new building 3. Women's Committee of the Buffalo Philharmonic 4. Tour, Albright-Knox Art Gallery Albany 1. Anniversary Observance of the Office of General Service of New York State 2. Governor's Club reception and dinner
  - New York, New York, October 24, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 720)
    1. Centennial Congress of the Eastern Territory of the Salvation Army 2. Cooperative Village Testimonial Dinner to honor Abraham E. Kazan
  - New York, New York, October 25, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 721)
    1. New York State Memorial to Dag Hammarsjkold 2. WOR-TV taping, "Problems of the Elderly"
  - Syracuse, New York; Ithaca, New York, October 26, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 722)
    Syracuse 1. New York State School Boards Association 2. News conference Ithaca 1. Cornell University new building dedication
  - New York, New York, October 27, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 723)
    1. New York State Traffic Safety Council 2. Young Men's Philanthropic League
  - New York, New York; Albany, New York; Greenville, New York, October 28, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 724)
    New York City 1. Clean Waters Luncheon, Associated Industries of New York State Albany 1. Appearance, Department of Health Greenville 1. Green County Republican Club Dinner
  - New York, New York, October 29, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 725)
    1. WNBC-TV taping, "Man in Office"
  - New York, New York, October 31, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 726)
    1. Yeshiva University new school ground breaking
  - Regrets, October 1965 (Box 24, Folder 727)
    1. Medical Correctional Association 2. Pulaski Day ceremonies, Pulaski, New York
  - New York, New York, November 4, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 728)
    1. Calvin Bullock Forum 2. Gala Preview of the New Dutch Galleries
  - New York, New York; Binghamton, New York, November 5, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 729)
    New York City 1. WABC-TV taping, "Issues and Answers" Binghamton 1. Appalachian Program Informational Meeting 2. "Binghamton Press," new plant tour
  - Staten Island, New York, November 8, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 730)
    1. Town meeting with recreation and conservation leaders at High Rock Conservation Center 2. Staten Island Chamber of Commerce Luncheon 3. Start Center for Girls dedication 4. Meeting, Director of Willowbrook State School 5. Town meeting on employment, commerce, housing and education
  - Atlanta, Georgia, November 9, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 731)
    1. Clean Waters Congress of the National Association of Counties Research
  - Plattsburgh, New York, November 12, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 732)
    1. Meeting with local leaders 2. Town meeting with industry and labor leaders 3. Local service clubs luncheon 4. Town meeting with conservation and agricultural leaders 5. Town meeting with educational leaders 6. Private dinner with news media leaders 7. General public town meetin
  - New York, New York, November 15, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 733)
    1. Manhattan State Hospital new construction 2. Special meeting with anti-poverty leaders 3. Private luncheon with crime and law enforcement leaders 4. Special meeting with housing leaders 5. General town meeting with industry and labor leaders 6. Charles Evans Hughes Dinner of the National Conference of Christians and Jews
  - Schenectady, New York; Washington, DC, November 17, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 734)
    Schenectady 1. Special meeting with industry and commerce leaders 2. Regional planning luncheon Washington, D.C. 1. White House Dinner to honor Princess Margaret and the Earl of Snowden
  - Albany, New York, November 18, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 735)
    1. Special meeting with hospital and health care leaders 2. Special meeting with crime and law enforcement leaders 3. Private dinner with news media leaders 4. Public town meeting
  - Brooklyn, New York; New York, New York, November 19, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 736)
    Brooklyn 1. Special meeting on medical rehabilitation 2. Luncheon meeting on elementary and secondary education 3. Meeting with school officials and visit to Public School 39 4. General public meeting on jobs and commerce New York City 1. National Association of Mental Health 2. Reception, dinner, ball to honor Princess Margaret and the Earl of Snowden
  - Rockland County, New York; New York, New York, November 22, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 737)
    Rockland County 1. Gold Key Club fund raising breakfast New York City 1. Testimonial dinner to honor Lowell Thomas
  - White Plains, New York, November 23, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 738)
    1. New Sears Roebuck store ground breaking
  - Cattaraugus and Chautauqua Counties, New York, November 24, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 739)
    1. Olean - Public meeting on education, jobs, commerce and conservation 2. Olean - Chamber of Commerce Luncheon 3. Salamanca - Seneca School new buildings 4. Jamestown - Public meeting on education, jobs, commerce and conservation 5. Lake Chautauqua - Special meeting with conservation leaders
  - Syracuse, New York, November 29, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 740)
    1. Special meeting on crime and juvenile delinquency 2. Luncheon meeting with hospital and health care leaders 3. Special meeting with education leaders 4. Special meeting with industry and commerce leaders 5. Private dinner with news media leaders 6. General public meeting